It is my absolute pleasure to introduce you to my amazing colleagues,
十分荣幸能向你介绍我那些才华横溢的同事
who will guide you throughout this program.
他们将引导你学习这个纳米学位
Juno Lee is a former data scientist,
Juno Lee 曾是数据科学家
who built neural networks for optimizing users shopping experiences.
负责打造神经网络以优化用户购物体验
In this program, Juno will focus on programming tools specifically Python,
在本课程中 Juno 负责讲解编程工具 具体来讲就是 Python
one of the most widely used programming languages in the industry.
这是业内应用最广的编程语言之一
Juan Delgado, a computational physicist with a Masters in Astronomy.
Juan Delgado 是一位计算物理学家 拥有天文学硕士学位
He previously worked for NASA,
他曾在 NASA 任职
developing space instruments using machine learning techniques.
负责用机器学习技术开发航天仪器
Juan will teach you some of the programming tools you will need to know.
Juna 负责讲授一些重要的编程工具
Mike Yee, who holds a Bachelor's of Science in mathematics and statistics,
Mike Yee 是数学与统计学理学士
and received his PhD in cognitive science.
认知科学博士
Mike will teach you Matplotlib,
他负责讲授 Matplotlib
the most mature Python package for data visualization.
也即 Python 最成熟的数据可视化包
Jennifer Stab, holds a PhD in Computer Science,
Jennifer Stab 是计算机科学博士
and Masters in Bio-statistics,
和生物统计学硕士
and was a university Professor of Analytics and Computer Science.
他也是一位大学教授 负责讲授分析学与计算机科学
Jennifer will take you step by step through some of the labs in this nano degree.
在本纳米学位课程中 Jennifer 负责讲解 lab 的一些操作
The labs will be short implementations in code,
lab 会要求你运用稍后学到的理论知识
of the theory you will have learned before.
实现一些简短的代码
Grant Sanderson, is a creator of the YouTube channel 3Blue1Brown,
Grant Sanderson 是 YouTube 3Blue1Brown 频道的主创人
which is dedicated to teaching math visually using a custom build animation tool.
使用自制动画工具 他致力于用生动的动画来讲解数学知识
He was previously a content creator at Khan Academy.
他曾是可汗学院的一位老师
Grant will bring you the beautiful visual world of linear algebra.
他将带你走进线性代数的世界 给你一场美妙的视觉体验
Luis Serrano, who worked as a machine learning engineer at Google.
Luis Serrano 曾是谷歌的机器学习工程师
He holds a PhD in Mathematics from the University of Michigan,
是密歇根大学的数学博士
and a Postdoctoral Fellowship at the University of Quebec at Montreal.
和魁北克大学蒙特利尔分校的博士后
Luis will teach you all you need to know about neural networks.
Luis 负责讲授神经网络的一切必要知识
Mat Leonard, a former Physicist,
Mat Leonard 曾是物理学家、
Research Neuroscientist and Data scientist.
神经科学家及数据科学家
He completed his PhD and Postdoctoral
加州大学伯克利分校的
Fellowship at the University of California in Berkeley.
博士和博士后
You will see Mat throughout the program in various lessons such as Pytorch.
若干课程部分都是由 Mat 负责讲授的 如 PyTorch 一节
He will also help you create your first project at Udacity, in image classifier.
他还会协助你完成在优达学城的第一个项目 图像分类器
We are very proud of our diverse community of teachers in the school of AI,
人工智能学院的教师人才辈出 我们十分自豪
and can't wait to start teaching you.
也等不及要同你分享他们的知识了